Proper, Carl UNITE Papers 6000/057
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Carl Proper UNITE Papers
1967-2005
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Proper, Carl
Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees
6000/057
3.5 cubic feet
3.5 linear ft.
Papers.
8686980
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives 227 Ives Hall Tower Road Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheelref@cornell.edu https://catherwood.library.cornell.edu/kheel/
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, June 25, 2015
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 30, 2015
8686980
- Garment 2000 - 1996 Regional Garment Industry, California, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- California Affidavit, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- California Garment Legislation, DoL Crackdown, and News Clippings, 1991-1999 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Scope and Contents
  Chinese News Clipping
- Sweatshop "Model Contract" and ILGWU in San Francisco Chinatown, 1991-1999 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Chadwick's of Boston, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Chadwick's Engineering Standards, 2000-2005 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Chadwick's Labor-Management Discussion, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Chadwick's Training - 2000 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- CAF Database/Computer, 1992-1995 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- CAF Fund Legal Issues, CAF Fund 1996-1997, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- CAF Fund Board (1997,1999) and Meetings (1994-1995), 1994-1999 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- CAF Fund Report 1996-2001 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- CAF Fund Ergonomics, 1994-2000 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- CAF Fund Meeting (Dec.15 2000) (Box 1, Folder 14)
- CAF Incorporation, Planning Group, and Steering Committee, 1990-1995 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Irwin Kahn and Marcus & Weisen, 1992-2000 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Shimmy Cohen Engineering, 1994-1997 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Shimmy Cohen Engineering, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Dr. Joyce Brown, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- AICP, 1999-2001 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- CMA and Dynamic Change in the Garment Industry, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Fashion Center Bid, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Fashioning and Industrial Strategy for Garment Workers, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation, 1997-2000 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Garment Industry Competitiveness Project, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- GIDC-CDF Discussion, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- NYTRN Survey Comments, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Robert Pauls, Expert, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Norma Rantisi: How New Industrial Districts Revive Older Ones, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Standard's Training GIDC, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Duke Conference on Global Apparel Production (Part 1), 1997 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Duke Conference on Global Apparel Production (Part 2), 1997 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Global Fairness (Misc. and News Clippings), 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Global/ITC Database, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Briones International and International Affairs Department Alan Howard, 1996-2000 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- ICO/ITG - International Labor, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- ITG-ICO 1999 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Asia Talk + APEC, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Country Reports - Pacific Rim Conference, April 1997 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- China and Prison Labor in China, 1991-1997 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- WTO China and Hong Kong, 1997-2000 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- India, Indonesia, Fiji Incentives and union Labels, 1997-2000 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Zensen/UNITE Joint Statement, Japan, 1992-1999 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Malaysia and inter-American Regional Organization of Workers, 1997-2001 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- ITGLWF Maquila Organizing Project, Free Trade Areas of the Americas, STITCH, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Ecuador, Dominican Republic, Guatemala, Honduras, and Mexico, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- European Letter, Australian Unions, Irish Unions, Germany, ITG Montreal, South Africa, 1996-1998 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Ron Karpman, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Ron Karpman (Misc.), 1998-2001 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Rank Assessment and Apparel Costing, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Carlcraft Knit Sales, 1996-2000 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Carnival Creations, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Ron Karpman: Immigration Letters, La Del Fashion, Malden Mills, and Schedules, 1999-2001 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Morley Shirts, Nygard, Roller Fabric, and V.C. Sportswear, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Andrea Co., 1989 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Sol Chaikin Essay, 1972-1975 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Contractors and Contractor Jobs for Selected Jobbers, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Mitch Likiec and Job Evaluation, 1967-1988 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Needle Trades Action Project, 1985-1993 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Needle Trades Action Project (New England) Board of Directors Minutes, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Needle Trades Action Project (New England) Producer Cooperative, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Needle Trades Action Project (New England) Report, 1985-1990 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Needle Trades Action Project (New England) Training Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Assessment of Clinical Competency, 2002-2004 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Consortium for Quality Nurse Practitioner Education, 1999-2003 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Continuous Quality Improvement, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Evaluation Task Force, 2005-2007 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Special Task Force, 1999-2001 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Sweatshops, 1988-1999 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Sweatshops: California, Emails, Enforcement, GAO Study, Issues, and Media, 1994-1999 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Misery by Design, Sweatshop Standards, Union Memos, 1992-1997 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- USAS Proposal to ILGWU, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Engineering Projects to Upgrade UNITE Firms, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Chinatown Contractors, Compensation, and Employee Leasing, 1993-1995 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Engineering 2004-2005, Contract Language, and Legal Issues, 1963-2005 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Garment Worker Statistics, 1950-1989 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Guide for Operating Prices, 1961-1962 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Hubbard (2000) and Jobbers and Contractor Jobs for Selected Contractors (1994), 1994-2000 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Modular Guide, 1991-1998 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Modular Manufacturing Articles (1991-1997) and Price Settlement Guide (1975), 1975-1997 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- The Process of Job Evaluation and the Occupations of the Garment Industry, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Regional Statistics Comparisons (1947-1994) and Retail Performance Measures and the Sourcing Decision (1997), 1947-1997 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Retail Research Reports and Sourcing Cost Comparison Statistics, 1998-2000 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Structure of Apparel Industry (1987-1997), Time Study by Irwin Kahn, and Union Membership Charts (1930-1995), 1930-1997 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Textile Apparel Connection (1995-1999) and Converters (1990-1997), 1990-1999 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Industry Situation from 1996 FMCS Grant Proposal (1996), Textiles in Italy, and Malden Mills Inspection Grievance (2001), 1996- 2001 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- American Great Mills (Textile Industry), 1984-1994 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Textiles: Statistics and US vs. Imported, 1990-1996 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Chapters 3-5 from Book on Textile Industry (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Carter Industries and Eagle Knit, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Economic Policy Institute, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Italian American Labor Council (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Lawrence History Center (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Labor History Photos (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Labor Union Growth, Decline (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Membership, Mid-Atlantic states - PA, MD, W.VA (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Negotiations - 2001 Local 23-25 -- Pocono Seminar (Box 4, Folder 6)
- New York Dress Board Settlement (Box 4, Folder 7)
- News clippings (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Obama support letter - Propper Int'l. (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Organizing - (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Phone complaints (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Political Department (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Pucci (Box 4, Folder 13)
- UNITE! Employee Handbook Updates, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- UNITE! For a better future (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Worker Organization, Human Resource Practices, and Firm Performance (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Worker Rights in the Americas? A rare inside glimpse, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Handwritten notes (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Proper Family History (Box 4, Folder 19)
- 3.5" floppies labeled (Box 4, Folder 20)
- 3.5" floppies unlabeled (Box 4, Folder 21)
- ILGWU Plaque (Box 4, Folder 22)